sanmiguelguide.com 2010-12-29

# SanmiguelGuide.com Privacy Policy

## SanMiguelGuide.com Privacy Policy

## Third-Party Advertising Privacy Policy

We use third-party advertising companies such as Google Inc. to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on their visit to our site and other sites on the Internet. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please visit their policy page by [clicking here](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

## Anonymous Information Collected on this Website

We use third-party advertising companies such as Google Inc. to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on their visit to our site and other sites on the Internet. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please visit their policy page by [clicking here](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

## Changes To Our Privacy Policy

We reserve the right to amend this Privacy Policy at any time, for any reason. Notice of such amendments will be posted as an updated Privacy Policy on this website, and an effective date will be indicated. Users are encouraged to check our site frequently to review the current Privacy Policy in effect.
